colum.edu 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Columbia College Chicago

## Your Personal Information

Columbia College Chicago respects your privacy. We will never give, sell, rent, or share your personal information with any person or company in any way not listed here, unless compelled by law. 

## Cookies

We use cookies to remember if you have visited our site. You have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on your browsers. If you opt to disable cookies, you will still be able to use our website.

## Remarketing

We use remarketing services from Google and other providers. These providers use cookies to remember when you have visited our site and display our ads to you on other websites. You can opt out of these cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

## Web Analytics

We use Google Analytics and other cookie or IP address-based tools to analyze website visitor behavior and technical information for reporting and marketing purposes. The information analyzed may include any personal details you voluntarily provide through online forms. You can find [more information about how Google uses data](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), you can also prevent Google Analytics from using your data by downloading and installing the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

## Sharing

We sometimes share aggregate demographic information with our partners. This information is not connected to your personal information. We share personal information with third parties as required to process that information or provide services available on Columbia College Chicago websites. Third parties are required not to share personal information.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. We have no control over the privacy practices of sites not owned by Columbia College Chicago.

## Security

Columbia College Chicago takes extensive precautions to protect your information, and we have security measures in place to protect the information under our control.

## Compliance and Cooperation With Regulatory Authorities

Columbia College Chicago complies with and works with appropriate regulatory authorities to ensure compliance with all applicable laws, including the [Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)](http://www.colum.edu/ferpa). Any applicable laws supersede this privacy policy.

## Notification of Changes

If we change this privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site.
